<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Canadian Red Cross</title>
	<atom:link href="/category/uncategorized/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:10:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/03/cropped-images-Copy-1-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Uncategorized &#8211; Canadian Red Cross</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>The tiger of that time</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/the-tiger-of-that-time/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/the-tiger-of-that-time/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:10:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=25</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[You must know that there were animals in those days that are no longer seen today. The four-tusked elephant, the thirty cubit long crocodile or the grinning three-horned rhinoceros of those days, none of these are found today. Sometimes, on the rocks or under the ice in caves, some traces of their skeletons are found ... <a title="The tiger of that time" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/the-tiger-of-that-time/" aria-label="Read more about The tiger of that time">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You must know that there were animals in those days that are no longer seen today. The four-tusked elephant, the thirty cubit long crocodile or the grinning three-horned rhinoceros of those days, none of these are found today. Sometimes, on the rocks or under the ice in caves, some traces of their skeletons are found &#8211; from which scholars know that such and such beasts once existed on earth. Those who practice all these things can tell by looking at the teeth little by little &#8211; what kind of animal&#8217;s teeth it is, whether it eats meat or is vegetarian, etc.</p>
<p>The animal I am talking about is called Sabre-toothed Tiger in English. Its skeletons have been found in Europe, America, our country and many other places. It is difficult to say what he did with these sword-like teeth. It is not convenient to bite with such long teeth; Also, this tiger&#8217;s jawbone was not as strong as that of today&#8217;s tigers, so its bite force was less.</p>
<p>The teeth were about six inches long, with knife-like edges—perhaps useful for slicing off prey.<br />
The appearance and color of the animal changes according to the conditions in which it lives. The black spots on the tiger&#8217;s body can tell you that it has a habit of moving in the bush&#8211;when the tiger hides in the thickets of grass, the yellow-black stripes of the tiger mix with the light and shadow of the tall grass in such a way that you can tell at a glance. Not that there is anything but bushes. But as far as we can tell, it seems that our saber tooth lived in the open as much as Monsieur Sinha—so it&#8217;s possible that he didn&#8217;t have the tiger-like markings he once did.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/the-tiger-of-that-time/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Who is called the fundamental particle in nuclear physics?</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/who-is-called-the-fundamental-particle-in-nuclear-physics/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/who-is-called-the-fundamental-particle-in-nuclear-physics/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:09:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=23</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What rote is a bit. Ratna remains for ages. But history may not write the name of the first slanderer. Khanar&#8217;s vachanas cannot be compared to ratna in a negative sense, however, his sloka-vachanas have been passed down through the ages for hundreds of thousands of years. Even today, the form-juice-smell of Khanar&#8217;s speech has ... <a title="Who is called the fundamental particle in nuclear physics?" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/who-is-called-the-fundamental-particle-in-nuclear-physics/" aria-label="Read more about Who is called the fundamental particle in nuclear physics?">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>What rote is a bit. Ratna remains for ages. But history may not write the name of the first slanderer. Khanar&#8217;s vachanas cannot be compared to ratna in a negative sense, however, his sloka-vachanas have been passed down through the ages for hundreds of thousands of years.</p>
<p>Even today, the form-juice-smell of Khanar&#8217;s speech has not faded so much. But who was Khana, when he lived in the world, that information is not recorded in irrefutable documents in history, but the sayings that have been spoken by people for ages are not completely false, so it can be emphasized that there was someone behind it.<br />
Who is he?</p>
<p>There are several legends about who Khanna was and when he was. Some of it is close to the truth, some is full of lies.</p>
<p>Let&#8217;s talk about myths later, let&#8217;s turn our eyes to history first. Khana is believed to have been born around 800 AD, in Chandraketugarh, near Barasat in present-day North Twenty-four Parganas district. Khan&#8217;s father&#8217;s name is Atnacharya. This also has no historical basis, the idea is derived from a verse by Khana, where Khana says: &#8216;I am Attanacharya&#8217;s daughter, Gante-gante kare na or anati.<br />
&#8216;<br />
Excavation of the ruins of Chandraketugarh in Barasa has not been completed yet. The historical foundation of Khana who lived here is not strong. But those who do research on history, many times they have to combine folklore and documents, find some patterns and match two by two by four. Proverb-Imperial history and folklore researcher of Bengal. Dinesh Chandra Sen wrote, Khana&#8217;s husband Mihir lived for many days in a place called Chandrapur, and this Chandrapur was a center of Chandraketurajya. After nearly a hundred years, when the remains of Chandraketu Gar were really found in Barasa, people assumed that Barah-Mihir-Khanai or why should it be left, this was the house of Khana-Mihir.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/who-is-called-the-fundamental-particle-in-nuclear-physics/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Slimane&#8217;s thug campaign</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/slimanes-thug-campaign/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/slimanes-thug-campaign/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=21</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[There are scams all over India. The world&#8217;s most violent killers are roaming in the streets of the city, deserts, rivers and mountains in disguise. But no one believes this except one. He is William Henry Sleeman. People laugh at Henri Slimane. No one wants to believe him. Thuggi may have once existed in India, ... <a title="Slimane&#8217;s thug campaign" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/slimanes-thug-campaign/" aria-label="Read more about Slimane&#8217;s thug campaign">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>There are scams all over India. The world&#8217;s most violent killers are roaming in the streets of the city, deserts, rivers and mountains in disguise. But no one believes this except one. He is William Henry Sleeman.</p>
<p>People laugh at Henri Slimane. No one wants to believe him. Thuggi may have once existed in India, but in the last 100 years no trace of Thuggi has been found. But Slimane has a firm belief, thugs.</p>
<p>But no one knows about them. Surprise, surprise!<br />
In 1809, the young Henry Sleeman came to India from England with a passion for adventure. He then joined the army of the East India Company as a soldier. Needed improved.</p>
<p>He had all the qualities of a great soldier. Suddenly, an old book found in the Fort William College Library in Calcutta messed up Slimane&#8217;s life.<br />
The author of the book is a French traveler named M. Thivenot. The book is full of unknown stories of the terrible killers called thugs. Very true story.</p>
<p>But the story ends there. The book is almost 100 years old. &#8216;What else is there thugs? If there is no, who suppressed them?&#8217; Slimane asked himself. Acquaintances and strangers ask about thugs. But no one can tell their news. You must find yourself on the road, in the gathering of pilgrims, in the temple, in the Kachari of Moral, in the field, in the ghat, in the fair, in the tangle of people. The thugs found new stories in bundles of old papers in the library and office.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/slimanes-thug-campaign/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Description of women in the Holy Qur&#8217;an</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/description-of-women-in-the-holy-quran/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/description-of-women-in-the-holy-quran/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:08:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=19</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Almighty Allah has declared mankind as the best of creation, half of which is women. The status of women in Islam is immense. In the Holy Qur&#8217;an, there are discussions about different women in different contexts. Some of whom are wives of prophets, some are mothers of prophets. Today we will try to know briefly ... <a title="Description of women in the Holy Qur&#8217;an" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/description-of-women-in-the-holy-quran/" aria-label="Read more about Description of women in the Holy Qur&#8217;an">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Almighty Allah has declared mankind as the best of creation, half of which is women. The status of women in Islam is immense. In the Holy Qur&#8217;an, there are discussions about different women in different contexts. Some of whom are wives of prophets, some are mothers of prophets.</p>
<p>Today we will try to know briefly about the women discussed in the Holy Quran, Inshallah.<br />
Hawa (A.): Hawa (A.) is the mother of mankind. Consort of Adam (A.S.). His discussion has come in the Holy Qur&#8217;an.</p>
<p>It was narrated, &#8216;And I said, O Adam, dwell thou and thy wife in Paradise, and eat of it at ease, according to thy will, and do not approach this tree, lest thou be among the wrongdoers.&#8217; (Surah: Baqarah, Verses: 35-36)<br />
Sarah (A.S.): She is one of the wives of Ibrahim (A.S.). The Holy Qur&#8217;an mentions the fact that God Almighty gave him the good news of giving him a child. It is said, &#8216;And his wife was standing, he laughed.</p>
<p>Then I gave him the glad tidings of Isaac and after Isaac of Jacob.&#8217; (Surah: Hud, verse: 71)<br />
Hajar (A.S.): She is also a wife of Ibrahim (A.S.), mother of Ishmael (A.S.). On the instructions of Almighty Allah, Ibrahim (A.S.) left him in the uninhabited valley or Kaaba courtyard. The incident is mentioned in the Holy Qur&#8217;an, which also indirectly mentions Hagar. It has been said, &#8216;O our Lord, I have indeed settled some of my progeny in a barren valley near Your Sacred House, O our Lord, so that they may establish the prayer.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/description-of-women-in-the-holy-quran/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>During the days of Friday, sins are forgiven</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/during-the-days-of-friday-sins-are-forgiven/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/during-the-days-of-friday-sins-are-forgiven/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:08:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The importance of Friday is immense. Friday is the weekly Eid for Muslims. The importance and significance of Juma is so great that a separate Surah named &#8216;Juma&#8217; has been revealed in the Qur&#8217;an. It is mentioned in Surah Juma of the Qur&#8217;an: &#8216;O believers! When the call to prayer is called on the day ... <a title="During the days of Friday, sins are forgiven" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/during-the-days-of-friday-sins-are-forgiven/" aria-label="Read more about During the days of Friday, sins are forgiven">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The importance of Friday is immense. Friday is the weekly Eid for Muslims. The importance and significance of Juma is so great that a separate Surah named &#8216;Juma&#8217; has been revealed in the Qur&#8217;an. It is mentioned in Surah Juma of the Qur&#8217;an: &#8216;O believers! When the call to prayer is called on the day of Friday, proceed to the remembrance of Allah (to the mosque) and leave off (all worldly activities).</p>
<p>It is good for you, if you only knew.&#8217; (Surah: Juma, verse: 9)<br />
Juma&#8217;s Day</p>
<p>The most important act of Friday is to perform Friday prayers with great importance. This is the most virtuous act of Friday. Many virtues of Friday prayers have been described in the hadith.</p>
<p>Friday prayers are forgiven</p>
<p>Humans are prone to sin. According to the hadith, the sins of the previous week are forgiven through Friday prayers. Abu Huraira (RA) said, Rasulullah (SAW) said, “Whoever takes a bath on Friday, wears good clothes and uses perfume if he has one, then comes to the Friday prayer and does not go forward with his head over other worshippers. Performs prescribed prayers. Then the imam remains silent from the time he comes out for the khutbah until the salam, then this deed of his will be expiation for all his sins from the previous Friday to the next Friday.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/during-the-days-of-friday-sins-are-forgiven/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saudi Arabia&#8217;s new guidelines on performing Tawaf of the Holy Kaaba</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/saudi-arabias-new-guidelines-on-performing-tawaf-of-the-holy-kaaba/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/saudi-arabias-new-guidelines-on-performing-tawaf-of-the-holy-kaaba/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:07:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=15</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia has issued new instructions on the Tawaf of the Holy Kaaba on the occasion of the upcoming month of Ramadan. According to the new guidelines, only those performing Umrah can circumambulate the Holy Kaaba. And ordinary Muslims are asked to pray inside the mosque. This initiative is taken to ensure the safety and ... <a title="Saudi Arabia&#8217;s new guidelines on performing Tawaf of the Holy Kaaba" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/saudi-arabias-new-guidelines-on-performing-tawaf-of-the-holy-kaaba/" aria-label="Read more about Saudi Arabia&#8217;s new guidelines on performing Tawaf of the Holy Kaaba">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Saudi Arabia has issued new instructions on the Tawaf of the Holy Kaaba on the occasion of the upcoming month of Ramadan. According to the new guidelines, only those performing Umrah can circumambulate the Holy Kaaba. And ordinary Muslims are asked to pray inside the mosque. This initiative is taken to ensure the safety and comfort of Umrah pilgrims.</p>
<p>This information was given in a statement by the General Presidency Department, which manages the Holy Mosque.<br />
Entry into the Holy Kaaba premises was strictly controlled since the Corona period. Only those performing Umrah could enter there. No one could enter there if he wanted to perform Tawaf normally.</p>
<p>And according to the new instructions, now the worshipers will not be able to pray in front of the Kaaba. Many people think that such an initiative has been taken to control the overflowing crowd of Umrah pilgrims in the upcoming month of Ramadan.<br />
Meanwhile, one imam has been reassigned to the Holy Masjid al-Haram and two to the Prophet&#8217;s Mosque. They are Dr. Yasir Bin Rashid Al-Dawsari, Dr. Khalid Bin Sulaiman Al-Muhanna and Dr. Ahmad Bin Ali Al-Huzayfi.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/saudi-arabias-new-guidelines-on-performing-tawaf-of-the-holy-kaaba/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>America dominates the world&#8217;s richest women</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/america-dominates-the-worlds-richest-women/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/america-dominates-the-worlds-richest-women/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:07:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The list of the world&#8217;s top richest women is dominated by the US as always. However, along with China, India is also coming forward in this list. Some of them are billionaires through inheritance, but many are becoming billionaires through self-efforts by building technology companies. The financial services company City Index has published the list ... <a title="America dominates the world&#8217;s richest women" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/america-dominates-the-worlds-richest-women/" aria-label="Read more about America dominates the world&#8217;s richest women">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The list of the world&#8217;s top richest women is dominated by the US as always. However, along with China, India is also coming forward in this list. Some of them are billionaires through inheritance, but many are becoming billionaires through self-efforts by building technology companies. The financial services company City Index has published the list of countries according to the number of female billionaires around the International Women&#8217;s Day on March 8.</p>
<p>Forbes Magazine&#8217;s Live Billionaire Tracker has been used to compile this list.<br />
The United States is on the first place in this list. The number of female billionaires in the country is 97. China is second in the list.</p>
<p>The number of female billionaires in the country is 42. The country in the third position is Germany. There are 22 female billionaires in this country. Italy&#8217;s female billionaires are 19 in fourth place.<br />
India&#8217;s women billionaires are 15 in fifth place. Australia, Switzerland and Brazil have 9 people in sixth place. Hong Kong, Spain, Sweden and France each have seven people in seventh place. Canada and South Korea have 6 each in eighth place. Israel and Turkey have four each in ninth place.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/america-dominates-the-worlds-richest-women/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Inflation in February was 9.67 percent</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/inflation-in-february-was-9-67-percent/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/inflation-in-february-was-9-67-percent/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 17:06:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The government&#8217;s target for the current financial year is to keep inflation within 6 percent. But the crazy horse of inflation is not being managed at all. In February, the country&#8217;s inflation eased slightly from January to 9.67 percent. In January it was 9.86 percent. However, Bangladesh Bank has set the inflation target at 7.5 ... <a title="Inflation in February was 9.67 percent" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/inflation-in-february-was-9-67-percent/" aria-label="Read more about Inflation in February was 9.67 percent">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The government&#8217;s target for the current financial year is to keep inflation within 6 percent. But the crazy horse of inflation is not being managed at all. In February, the country&#8217;s inflation eased slightly from January to 9.67 percent. In January it was 9.86 percent.</p>
<p>However, Bangladesh Bank has set the inflation target at 7.5 percent in the second half monetary policy.<br />
According to the latest data of Bangladesh Bureau of Statistics, the country&#8217;s inflation rate in February is 9.67 percent. According to the sources of the Ministry of Planning, this updated information is known. Inflation of 9.67 percent means that if the price of a product in February 2023 is Tk 100, then in February 2024 it has to be bought at Tk 109 67 paise.</p>
<p>At this time, the average price inflation of food in the country is 9.56 percent, while the inflation of non-food products is 9.42 percent. Meanwhile, the inflation rate in rural areas is slightly lower than in urban areas. Rural inflation is 9.48 percent, while urban inflation is 9.88 percent. Bangladesh is in a major financial crisis due to high inflation.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/inflation-in-february-was-9-67-percent/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dubai work visa will be available in 5 days</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/dubai-work-visa-will-be-available-in-5-days/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/dubai-work-visa-will-be-available-in-5-days/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:57:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=9</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Good news for travelers. Dubai visa will be available in just five days. UAE authorities have recently reduced the processing time for work visas and residency visas. It used to take 30 days for Dubai visa processing earlier. Now that time has been reduced to just five days. Apart from this, as per the new ... <a title="Dubai work visa will be available in 5 days" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/dubai-work-visa-will-be-available-in-5-days/" aria-label="Read more about Dubai work visa will be available in 5 days">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Good news for travelers. Dubai visa will be available in just five days. UAE authorities have recently reduced the processing time for work visas and residency visas.</p>
<p>It used to take 30 days for Dubai visa processing earlier.</p>
<p>Now that time has been reduced to just five days. Apart from this, as per the new guidelines, instead of 16 documents, now only five documents will be required. Dubai&#8217;s Ruler and Vice President Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid announced the plan last Wednesday.<br />
Referring to the inauguration of the employment package, Mohammed bin Rashid said, the project is designed to speed up, simplify and streamline the residency and employment processes.</p>
<p>The new scheme will deal with services such as issuing work permits for employees and new employees, residency permit renewals, physical examinations for residency visas, work permit cancellations and Emirates ID fingerprint scans.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/dubai-work-visa-will-be-available-in-5-days/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Women&#8217;s participation in banking is increasing</title>
		<link>/2024/03/08/womens-participation-in-banking-is-increasing/</link>
					<comments>/2024/03/08/womens-participation-in-banking-is-increasing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 16:56:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Women workers are increasing in the banking sector. Employment of women in private and specialized banks has increased significantly. According to the latest data of Bangladesh Bank, by the end of 2023, the number of women workers in the country&#8217;s banking sector has increased to 33 thousand 346 people. Whereas at the end of 2022, this number was ... <a title="Women&#8217;s participation in banking is increasing" class="read-more" href="/2024/03/08/womens-participation-in-banking-is-increasing/" aria-label="Read more about Women&#8217;s participation in banking is increasing">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Women workers are increasing in the banking sector. Employment of women in private and specialized banks has increased significantly. According to the latest data of Bangladesh Bank, by the end of 2023, the number of women workers in the country&#8217;s banking sector has increased to 33 thousand 346 people. Whereas at the end of 2022, this number was 31 thousand 939 people.</p>
<p>Accordingly, the employment of women in the banking sector has increased. At present, the rate of female officers in the banking sector is 16.37 percent as compared to males.</p>
<p>On the other hand, 9 foreign commercial banks have the least number of female officers-employees (981 people), but the rate of female officers-employees in foreign commercial banks is higher than other banks, 24.18 percent.</p>
<p>Bankers reported that women&#8217;s participation in education has increased significantly.</p>
<p>So when job circulars are issued more applications are received from women job seekers. As the number of applicants increases, so does the recruitment of women. This is the primary reason for increasing the number of women officers in banks.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/2024/03/08/womens-participation-in-banking-is-increasing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 65/110 objects using Redis
Page Caching using Redis 
Database Caching using Redis

Served from: _ @ 2024-03-25 02:15:33 by W3 Total Cache
-->